Preliminary Inventory of the Benjamin Apthorp Gould Fuller Papers, 1915-1919
Hoover Institution Archives
Benjamin Apthorp Gould Fuller Papers,
1915-1919
XX095
Fuller, Benjamin Apthorp Gould, 1879-1956
4 manuscript boxes, 2 envelopes (1.8 linear feet)
Hoover Institution Archives Stanford, California 94305-6010
Memoranda, daily bulletins, and photographs, relating to military developments, especially on the Italian front, and to political conditions in Europe and Russia.
Administrative Information
Access
Collection open for research.
Biographical/Historical Note
Captain, United States Army; member, American Section, Supreme War Council of the Allied and Associated Powers, during World War I.
Scope and Content of Collection
Memoranda, daily bulletins, and photographs, relating to military developments, especially on the Italian front, and to political conditions in Europe and Russia.
Access Points
United States. Army. American Expeditionary Forces.; World War, 1914-1918.; World War, 1914-1918--Campaigns--Italy.; Europe.; Europe--Politics and government.; Soviet Union.; Russia (Federation); Soviet Union--History--Revolution, 1917-1921.; United States--Armed Forces.; Allied and Associated Powers (1914-1920) Supreme War Council.
Container List
- Bulletins, 1918 May 22-1919 June 3 (Box 1)
  - Military situations
  - Political situation - Allied countries (Box 2)
  - Political situation - Enemy countries
  - Political situation - Neutral countries (Box 3)
  - Russian situation
- Communiques from the Italian front, 1918 June 15-November 10 (Box 4)
- Italian military intelligence service, section M, series A. Bulletin, 1918 June 22 -November 7, nos. 600-736
- Italian military intelligence service, section M, series B. Bulletin, 1918 July 16 -October 1, nos. 17-18, 21-22
- Italian N. G., 1918 June 18-November 5, nos. 124-264
- Memoranda for General Bliss, 1918 May 27-1919 June 11